# Gomathi M

Computer Science graduate with two years of work experience in Full Stack Development. Interested to work in Full Stack Development, Data Analytics. Open to learn new technologies. Looking for a collaborative workplace with amazing people to work and learn with.

#### **Skills**

- Java
- Angular 5+
- Spring Framework
- Bootstrap
- REST

- Angular JS
- SQL Server
- Oracle
- Docker

# **Experience**

JAN 2017 - APRIL 2017

### Internship / iNautix Technologies, Chennai

Did an internship for three months and developed a Financial System for small scale businesses with AngularJS, Java, Bootstrap and Spring Framework.

JUN 2017 - PRESENT

# Application Developer / BNY Mellon Technology, Chennai

Held responsible for Depositary Receipt transactions and book closures. – Full Stack Development

- Worked with Angular 5+, Bootstrap & SASS for building responsive pages
- Engineered Real Time Data and transactions with SQL Server
- Used Spring Framework, Java and Maven to develop DR related core functions
- Worked on 15+ internal Batch Jobs with Spring Batch and UNIX
- Developed various REST Web Services to support demanding transactions
- Built, Deployed the application in Docker based cloud platform bxp3
- Constantly worked in Green Field Migration and resolved Security Vulnerabilities
- Worked on NEXEN Framework on demand for sub teams.

## **Education**

AUG 2018 - PRESENT

### M.Tech. Software Systems / BITS, Pilani

Pursuing M.Tech. Software Systems in BITS, Pilani as a work integrated learning program for keeping up to date with technologies and concepts like Machine Learning, Data Science and Artificial Intelligence.

JUN 2013- JUN 2017

# **B.Tech. Computer Science Engineering / Sastra University, Thanjavur**

Did Computer Science Engineering in Sastra University and attended various implants to learn new stuffs.

- Database Implant Training at Deep Dive Solutions, Chennai
- IT Implant Training at CoreEL Technologies, Bangalore

#### **Activities**

An active member of BNY Mellon's Corporate Social Responsibilities. Conducted and facilitated many programs and workshops for specially challenged children. Worked with Adyar Cancer Institute to help them set up database and query data efficiently. Volunteered and worked on Vehicle Pooling Application to ease travel & reduce carbon footprint for company employees.